Okay, it
's an external master's program,
and then we're going to try to do the
last gay class
[Music].
Ah,
the teacher was saying, and it must have the
four legs of the table: number one,
know your material about the content;
number two is, no, we're just going to
teach you how to present to a group; three,
behave professionally, good
behavior; number four,
how to organize a goal, how to pay for
it, how to pay your taxes, etc.,
the professional behavior of my
money and sex. It would be talking about the second one.
Today in Beijing, this news is
based on a night called "The
Garden of Hormones," in 10 million
images that go with this, but there are
like 35, and I think we'll just continue
in that attitude as a teacher, applying an
important part, as well as
professionals, how you behave
around other people of the
opposite sex, how you act towards women,
how men, actors, and men.
It's very surprising in the monastery, and
I lived, that they don't give them this
teaching, and many of the young people without a
campus come to Western countries.
I think I gave green cards to
eight of them, and six of them
abandoned their vows. This just has to be
done; it's
important, which is why we have to
talk if you're going  To be a teacher,
we should really talk about this
honestly, Dovizioso, and not be too
shy.
So, this edition doesn't have a sir
in
Haiti, although there is tension,
what would be death.
The parents of the children, the parents
tell them that there is a special ship that brings
the children, that it brings the children, that the
children don't know anything about sex, that
maybe when the child is already like 13 or
14, after the parents should
give them this talk because about
birth control, AIDS, intact,
and things like that,
and they were in Haiti. That's how I
want to teach it. Well, you already have the
images, and I'm going to go in order.
You have the first one,
Wasting, which is what's interesting:
the flowers and the trees of 2026, and in
the history of the West,
the trees, how the trees have
sex, man, that it was the monks, the
Christian monks in Europe
who were already discovering how the
trees have babies and the flowers.
A strange decision not to use English,
the base in Latin, and
trees
with Latin names and all the names,
but the flowers have
original flowers, the trees in sperm, the
flowers have  Ovules,
the words for the apple tree are
that they gave it Latin names
because it was a little embarrassed by the
fasting. So how do you know it's dead
from that picture? And they come
here, and these birds, the male has the
color red and the female has gray,
being gray,
this color of the birds. The difference
in color is that it's mainly
for reproduction. If men try
to see sexism, women,
this is the most important function of the
body.
So all animals and all those
that want to make more
of the same species don't want their
lineage to
come and want to continue having the same.
This is the main purpose of a
plant, it's the main one, so everything is
connected to trying to
keep themselves as a species.
Apple trees have to have sex, it's not an
option and it's the main reason they
come. Yes, they are 15 many years and they didn't
decide to use aero, no Latin words,
the one of the chalk in the West, I don't know in
China.
It's urgent in the human being, it's strong
like a nuclear bomb, all
living things, 6 trees, the fish, the birds and their
hands, their main theme of light, the
main theme of the body is to produce more of
the  The same thing is something very profound, a
moment of blind love,
love is blind, Don Quixote,
Pajín, I have studied, children of people,
finish the first page,
the mind is, love is blind because
hormones are blind, I live in Turin and we will do anything
to have another human,
Facebook started and the trees will give you anything to
have another tree and the
flowers too, it is something very very
strong and we all have it, I am
talking about someone else and we all
have it, all the teachers have it
too, all the students there
have it in Imex and Foundry, which is already being done
with flags, I am the same one
who
once I am telling you how to
help you because I already crashed, so it is
very powerful, we were like that, the most
powerful emotion in human beings and people don't
know, everywhere and nobody warns you,
barely a nuclear weapon between your legs,
name and good idea,
warns, my parents didn't tell me,
this cable,
I just discovered it, you know,
the main purpose of life was to
create more life and that is a good thing, without
nuclear force we would
not be here with our parents, they would
n't have made us,
Derek exists, this area is interesting
to study the parts  From a flower,
this is the style of the style of the
female part of this minister
and the other is the male part.
One has the last eggs and the other
has the external sperm, we call it
pollen.
In fact, it is possible for a flower to have
sex with itself so that the part, I'll
say, the male can make eggs and
that is in the female part and will have
another flower.
And that is the main goal of a
flower. And
this top will sneak into the sky in the woman,
also humans, and they don't look
so ashamed.
This is because I aspire to be beautiful
because flowers have a color, it's
beautiful, it's not because they are beautiful, it's because of
reproduction. Because it is true that
a flower can release semen between the
female part of the flower, but that would be
like a man with his sister, and
then the weaker genes. So it's
better if the sperm of one flower goes
to the vagina of another flower, it's better.
So you know why flowers are
so beautiful? Because they are trying to
attract the bee. The photos. Bees
have this thing in their stalks.
There is a juice that tastes good in the flower,
similar to the perfume that women wear.
With the bee  She just wants the
active juice that is clear by accident she's going to
fill up with Emporia sperm on her
legs a whole plan of God,
daisy to take when they left her
legs were already eating the human sperm
the beautiful flowers the only reason
Budanov and blew the flowers for you that
happy nap to have babies
[Music]
the flower is trying to attract the
bee so that all those
things stick to it and it can go to another flower and make the
lineage stronger and stronger.
In my yard, my garden, I
have a tree that produces wax
and there are female and male trees and I
think you can't sell my bed anymore, you ca
n't sell the female tree here
because they make a mess with the tails,
the fruit.
Then the flower gets pregnant,
you can use the first one, you can use the
first one, the same words, and then the
monks changed the names, they didn't
want to use the language, the language that isn't
because the flower gets pregnant into a
fruit, we don't need the color, we're already
pregnant
because the miniskirt already works, the flower,
in fact, from the fruit, which will be
inside the fruit,
in my new seed, in a woman
pregnant and a thousand babies and each one has
the power to make a thousand babies
is very powerful for the flower sequeira and
22 degrees and some bosses still with a rose-
based twist and they will produce seeds and
that will become the next
generation of roses.
The interesting thing is that when you grow
roses and you want them to be
healthy, they all get
old, you cut them off because the plant will
put all its energy into making new
seeds rather than trying to get
pregnant again. And you cut the
old roses, the plant says, "Oh no,
I abort, there's no need for another flower."
While the plant is going to be another new
flower, it will try to attract again. That's where
this desire to repeat begins, and if it
can repeat, the acidity and maintaining
the species is the
strongest instinct in plants.
And the fruit
is like milk for the baby.
If you want to have fun growing them for a few days and
don't pick them, you like them and they go everywhere.
Then the seed will
be in the old one, in the milk, and it will
grow to be very strong and have
100 melons. Then the fruit—the
purpose of the fruit is to feed the
baby.  and stealing and
baby food when they eat watermelon
because we're talking about fire, plants, and
flowers, and flowers,
Jacques Station, next image,
well, my family,
Vico
Ladies, women do the same thing
as flowers,
both, women are taught by their
culture,
you have to wear makeup, you have to be
beautiful, you have to wear clothes, 30, and that's been
going on for a thousand years, everyone
forgot because, like, you don't have, you don't
always think that, but your family in
your country, it's your
tough history, it tells you that you look good, they were
project makeup, you have to look
like a flower, but
Pierre Winner, vigor, that we need a
bee,
that's been thousands of years,
'all hormones, it's not fashion,
beauty, vinyl, we
need, already, I like fashion, I
like it, but to be honest, the original reason,
good, and makeup too,
men, well, because men are the ones who,
the bright colors of
men, shot at women, but
tourist, not knowing their culture,
designed it that way, and they saw it, you don't even
know what's going on,
you just do it, or you tell yourself, Inditex
face, mystic, or the television says that
I need this, my makeup, I'm going to
buy it  I'm going to buy then the whole
story of your culture quote for 56 years
brainwashing they do
n't wear makeup they're bad people they're
good they're lazy but she never told me
that her mom wouldn't let her leave the
house without lipstick and she has three or four
sisters and your mom is 94 we visited she's
lying down and in her bed you brought your
lipstick
don't tell Veronica that there isn't a
Veronica that I said
this the whole purpose of this is not it's not
safe it's not for fashion it's to
bring bees because because we need
more people if everyone stops having babies we're going to
stop humanity it would
stop it's something very powerful it's a
very powerful energy all
human beings have to make a baby and make
a baby
there's a difference between man and
woman
the bee and the flower
choose like the street yesterday if the first
administration is like 15-16
the flower you have this desire to have a
bee
as you approach 35
the ending of its mechanism any
then have someone I'm 35 and in
most of 40 because the desire of a
woman at 35
women at  35
with the ingenuity of bnamericas use and they
divorce, it's the same, but all they
want is a bee and they don't
understand, they don't have that urgency, they don't have to be going through it, they
just want to
know what's happening, they don't have to
be,
unfortunately, I looked it up, a
man's sperm is active, snide and
six up to the record of 96 and has the
same strong desire since 16, in 6th
woman, the woman goes down but the man
is always the same,
if you can stop it, it's good, it's like
trying to have the bees,
very powerful people, I'm going to have a
baby for you,
men are going to want to make places
up to the record, you left the 96 after
40, if a man has already made a baby,
the chances are greater, the
sperm
have problems with the sound in the
genetic material, so the men who
are hotter is up to 25 to
30, if something, if they want to have
sex,
this mafia and runs all the likes, part 2, it's
the mafia, those who are in the
prostitutes and the internet companies,
jazz in pornography, they are men, I
think 12 percent of all
men  In the world,
three and a half million is very good.
Pornography once a month
is a good percentage of all
men in the world. Howard, from all over the
world, young and well, at least once I'm
going to tell you what happened to you. The
page, hearing the jealousy, I'm joking,
we're talking about all this.
There are many flowers and bees in the
audience
available on the stage.
All the women respond and all the
men except
one woman. It doesn't matter how you look and
this action on the stage, it gets better. They
fall in love with the studio, with you. I've already
told you this story. Sometimes I sign a thousand
books on the phone at night and a
beautiful one sits down. We did
n't take a picture of her. I want to
tell her she's already gone and be aware that they're
not in love with you, they're
in love with the stage. If someone
stood up and taught them the same class, the
same woman would fall in love with that man. It doesn't
matter who's on the stage, they
just need a bee and they don't even
know that there's an urgency from
them and that they want to navigate and Veronese. They don't
even understand the desire, but they do
n't know where it comes from and they don't think about
it.
This teacher was saying, and this is very handsome.
I wonder if he has a wife.  The
purpose of this talk I had is for you to get
used to it,
and wait, it is, well, it's a
very powerful human force, and you're not Jaguars, Sting, you
're not especially beautiful,
they just have hormones,
and don't fall for it, don't fall for it, that's why he's in
love. He came to Miami, I don't
transform, Nash,
countless people have done it, there are many,
and many teachers have
made this mistake, and we had to
fire them because they've had
sex with all the girls in the class, and
not only men, women
can do it too. It's happened in classes,
yes, there are many women who
were with all the men in the
class, so understand about the
flowers and the bees, and when it
happens on stage and someone falls in
love with you
[Music]
the women at the rock and
roll concert, that beautiful Andy, her underwear on
stage, just let it go, they don't
care, it's their hormones, I'm sorry, it's not
very romantic. Of course, some people fall in
love, and that's okay, and I did, and it's
code, read, they did it too, for
example, but in May they did it.
It seems there's a difference between
love, mature love, and love for
Good reasons and just hormones,
that's why I
have to tell you the difference at the end of my talk,
and here are some things you
can think about. Number one,
because of your hormones:
if two people ask you a question, and
you're a man,
one is a beautiful young woman and the other
is an older woman, and you're going to have to
answer the
young woman's question first, it's unconscious hormones,
completely unconscious hormones. So you have to be
careful, that's all. And you
have to treat all the
students the same, it doesn't matter if they're
young or
old, whether they're available
or not. Treat everyone the same.
If you find that you're answering the
young women's questions, then you have a problem. And
when you have the hormones issue, it's
good to have another teacher with you. It's
very good to teach in pairs
so your friend can make you
aware that you're only answering the
young women's questions. You say, "No,
stop doing that." So it's
good to have another person of the
opposite sex teaching with you so you
have a mental switch.  And check your reality,
treat people the same, tell your friends
if I don't treat people the same,
please tell me, thousands by Montermini, please tell me
that the hormones are running
through my body,
don't have inappropriate contact, many
countries have different rules about
who you can touch, in America the vice
presidents can kiss
people's hair, women's hair, or there are no
rules in each country, for example,
when I was in Mexico I once kissed
a woman on the cheek and she got angry
with me, she said, "Are you French? Here we are
Mexicans, here we think of both
cheeks," she said, "Sorry, or fifteen minutes ago I already
kissed both cheeks, it doesn't
mean you didn't like me." So it could have happened
that someone
who might be hot, I
need follow-up,
can I have your email or the to witch art,
there is magnitude, they might need to ask you, ask you
deeper questions,
and if they think it's pure then it's
okay, you can share email or chat, but
if you think it's not pure, then you
tell them, "If I'm teaching and
with Jon, I tell them, 'You know John is an
expert on that topic, talk to him, don't
talk to him,' and I'm giving you a
strategy  A real suggestion: if
someone tells you, "Can I have your email?" and
you think they might just want your
pollen, well, you know, I'm not very good
at this, but my friend is very good at it. If they
never contact you, it's because the friend
had a hormonal attack, okay?
[Music]
So what do I do if I meet someone
at an event in Asia and I really
like them, like Scott meets Bridge, I mean, he meets
John, he meets Koni at a
retreat, and then we're allowed, isn't it
possible that we could have a good
relationship? Sure, but my suggestion is to
talk to your partner and tell them, "
This is already attracted to this person. I don't have a
wife. I
'm thinking it would be nice to go out with
her." Make a real check, a real check,
with them. So if you think you have to have
12 wives in
a year, probably these hormones, and we don't
know, we don't understand. Hormones
talk to us, and we listen. We can't
change it, and I'm being honest
here because this causes a lot of problems.
[Music]
Also, remember to be open. There's more to it than just
saying, "
I'm attracted to this woman. I'm not
married. I want to go out with her, ask her out."
What would you think? How is someone
else?
Very well, but first meet her
mother. First, not her mother, no, I don't
know, first the mother because that's how it's going to be
seen. After that, there are no questions.
Always don't be silly. They're not going to look
like flowers for 50 years.
So be honest with yourself. Meet the
mother, and I don't know if you still think that's
your soulmate. I found my
soulmate,
so marry her. But be
honest with yourself. Many, many
marriages fail because the man
lost his hair or the woman got wrinkles, and
then they don't see each other anymore and they divorce.
Then comes
Ernesto Corazón. Marriage is a
lifelong commitment.
Find your wife at an event, and
if there's a teacher, then be honest.
In American marriages, they say to
be, plan, and celebrate. In
sickness and in old age, there is, may
death do us part. Even if you hang yourself badly, even if you get old,
even if I have to
take you to the hospital.
I want to be married to you because
Efe Myers,
teachers of Asia, and listen to his
students. We're going to have a
secret channel to manage the 6 and
Collins, so any student
can complain to you.  Secretly,
we're going to have a channel in the office for Pitt
to use the whistle. Then, four or
five students in the
class notice that the teacher is
doing weird things and they have no one to
talk to. We're going to have a
special email. They don't have to
tell us your name, but you can tell us that
the teacher has six girlfriends and that he has
a hormone problem. Sometimes the
student goes to the channel not because they don't like you, not because they don't get along with you,
but
because you're not doing anything. So the
office isn't stupid, well, a little,
but we're going to check it out. We're going to check it out.
First, we're not going to fire you as
soon as we get a letter.
If we get 10 letters, the first letter,
we'll check it out, okay?
As a teacher, you have to respect
other people's relationships,
especially married people, people
who already have a
committed relationship. Be very careful. What's the
rule? The general rule is
always
to keep in mind that it's as if your
husband or wife were there, as if
your wife were flirting with her.
So it's a very good rule.
Oh,
and respect it.  Physical boundaries
vary from country to country. Some countries
allow people to hug, like in Mexico. I
think it's natural that when you meet
someone, you hug them.
I believe it's born with rhythms. The "
don't touch me" line
is more about boundaries. The main issue is that
each country has its own customs.
Teachers in many countries teach these customs,
so you should learn the
customs of the place where you're teaching.
Ask your friends who are
organizing the event if this is a country
where hugs are common, or a country where high-
fives are common.
I found that after
50 years, the high-
five is very safe. Many people
hug, and I shake their hands. It
's very safe,
and people like it. It's like
American basketball; the Chinese
like American basketball. So
here in this image, this is a
Westerner shaking hands with an
Asian woman. It might not be appropriate; you may have
gone too far. You may have
crossed
the line in that country. You have to
learn the rules.
What does it mean? We should never
act affectionately with our
students. You shouldn't act like you're doing
your best.  Students, but realize what
the rules are in that country. Life
tells you what the limits are, and
so you should be affectionate, you should be
loving.
Scott likes to hug people, like, on the
side, like they're a friend. If
you pat someone, it means there's
a good job, but make sure it's
okay in that country before you do it. Otherwise,
you're going to hurt people.
And I say, the next thing is the legal problems.
So, I have friends who
studied at the yoga center 30 years ago, and it was the
largest yoga center in America. They worked for
30 years
to build that yoga center, very
hard. Then one of the teachers had
sex with one of the students. In fact, it was
a woman and a woman,
and the woman sued the yoga studio in
America. I don't know what the custom is in
China, but to have a lawsuit. And they won
the lawsuit, and they had to close and
sell the studio.
Thirty years of hard work destroyed in
one day by one of the teachers. Don't do
that, don't do that to them. If there are any tremors, they
traveled  Heart attack and besides work and
we love you in this job you have to
not forget that when you do
that kind of behavior you are
risking
legal problems you are risking
a lawsuit and it is possible that there will be a
lawsuit there is very possible
a person who cannot control their
children
the problem of bees can destroy and
if there is you can destroy Asia even if the
police even if the police don't catch you
the internet will catch you so
when you have a stronger attraction
towards someone try to remember this
okay try to remember that you are
hurting all the other teachers
Daisy there are so many people for 25 years
work so much so hard so many
translations building daimon
such an incredible woman hard work a
bee with hormones can destroy it
if it gets to the internet now it is so easy
these days if you want to put on the
internet
after smelling